# Ernesto C. Razo Jr.

razz.ernesto@gmail.com +63 906797 8160 El Salvador City, Misamis Oriental Philippines

### **Summary**

A front-end web developer with 3+ years of experience who is passionate about responsive web design, mobile-first approaches, and automated testing. Build an application using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and provide a thorough understanding of a front-end framework like Angular. I am self-motivated and loves to work with a team that gives feedbacks and critiques to enhance and expand my current skills.

#### Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (SY: 2018 - 2019)

Bukidnon State University Alubijid Satellite Campus Alubijid, Misamis Oriental, Philippines

### **Experiences**

Front-End Developer (2019 - Present)

Hyperstacks Inc.

Cagayan De Oro City, Misamis Oriental Philippines

- ① One of the developer for landing page using HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Create automated testing for better development.
- Build a CMS using Angular.

## Front-End Developer (2020 - Present)

Muuvment

- Develops component user interface from mock-up design.
- Integrates API from backend.
- Treate E2E testing.

#### Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git, SCSS, TypeScript, Bootstrap, Material UI, Angular, NativeScript, E2E & Unit Testing.

# Language

Cebuano, Tagalog & English